- What does that mean?
- It means if anyone displeases me...
(Leonard:)...I don't help them set up their printer.
(Penny:)You are so funny.
(Leonard:)Good. Remember that
when I take my shirt off.
(Penny:)- This is nice. I'm so glad we did this.
- Me too.
(Leonard:)So, what do you think,
are we gonna get back together?
(Penny:)Whoa, not so fast.
(Leonard:)I'm sorry, what did I say?
(Penny:)Leonard, you know I will always
have feelings for you...
(Penny:)- Oh, God.
- What?
You said "always."
You'll always have feelings for me.
- So?
- That sounds like something you'd say...
(Leonard:)...if you didn't want a relationship
with someone.
"This isn't working out,
but I'll always have feelings for you."
"I'm sorry I slept with your best friend,
"Here's the thing, Lisa,
I'm into dudes now...
(Leonard:)...but I'll always have feelings
for you."
- How would you say it?
- I have feelings for you.
(Penny:)- Same thing.
- No, it's not. "Always" made it worse.